<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Monster Job Search Results machine learning</title>
    <description>RSS Feed for Monster Job Search</description>
    <link>http://rss.jobsearch.monster.com/rssquery.ashx?q=machine+learning</link>
    <image>
      <title>Monster Job Search Results machine learning</title>
      <url>http://media.monster.com/mm/usen/my/144x30_monsterBug.gif</url>
      <link>http://rss.jobsearch.monster.com/rssquery.ashx?q=machine+learning</link>
      <width>144</width>
      <height>30</height>
    </image>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2019 Monster. All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <webMaster>RssJobSearch@monster.com</webMaster>
    <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 16:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <docs>http://backend.userland.com/rss</docs>
    <generator>RSS.NET: http://www.rssdotnet.com/</generator>
    <item>
      <title>REMOTE Senior Data Scientist - Machine Learning - 140K-200K</title>
      <description>NY-New York, Job Title: Senior Data Scientist Job Location: NYC, Seattle, LA, or REMOTE Salary: $140,000 - $200,000 Annual Base Salary DOE, Bonus, Full Covered Medical, Dental and Vision Benefits Requirements: At least 5 years with Data Mining, Machine Learning We are an exciting, growing company working with cross platforms - desktop and mobile. We have been around for over 10 years and have strong partnershi</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/REMOTE-Senior-Data-Scientist-Machine-Learning-140K-200K-Job-New-York-NY-US-221981844.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221981844</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 05:03:47 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer</title>
      <description>TX-Austin, Working in a high performing team for an AI technology consulting start-up, you will work projects end-to-end to deliver Artificial Intelligence &amp; Machine Learning solutions for customers on projects ranging from Deep Learning to Natural Language Processing to Computer Vision and more. They are a collaborative team that provides excellent training and are growing the ML team due to an increase in </description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Senior-Machine-Learning-Engineer-Job-Austin-TX-US-221167730.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221167730</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:05:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Scientist/Machine Learning Engineer</title>
      <description>CA-Palo Alto, AIC Talent Solutions is seeking qualified candidates for a Data Scientist/Machine Learning Engineer in Palo Alto, CA. This is a 6-month contract with excellent potential for long term extension or contract to hire. Green Card or US Citizens only as no sponsorship is available for this role. The ideal candidate will have a strong knowledge of ML, NLP, Deep Learning, Knowledge Graphs and have experi</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Data-Scientist-Machine-Learning-Engineer-Job-Palo-Alto-CA-US-221592793.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221592793</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:16:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Scientist/Machine Learning Engineer</title>
      <description>CA-Palo Alto, Location: Palo Alto, CA Salary: Open Description: Our client is currently seeking a Data Scientist/Machine Learning Engineer This is a W2 only position. No C2C candidates will be accepted. We are looking for a Data Scientist/ML Engineer to join our technology team to solve exciting business problems in the domain of commercial banking, payments and financial services. Candidates must have a strong</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Data-Scientist-Machine-Learning-Engineer-Job-Palo-Alto-CA-US-221582642.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221582642</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:02:26 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sr. Statistical Programmer - Machine Learning/Advanced Analytics</title>
      <description>TX-Plano, Job Description We have an exciting opportunity for a Sr. Statistical Programmer - Machine Learning/Advanced Analytics with our industry-leading client in Plano, TX. We will accept corp to corp or w2 contractors. For our w2 consultants, we offer a great benefits package that includes Medical, Dental, and Vision benefits, 401k with company matching, and life insurance. Responsibilities: Perform rev</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Sr-Statistical-Programmer-Machine-Learning-Advanced-Analytics-Job-Plano-TX-US-221976220.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221976220</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 19:37:29 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Engineer - Computer Vision</title>
      <description>CO-Denver, Position: Machine Learning Engineer with Computer Vision experience Location: 100% Remote Salary:DOE We are an industry leading software company catering to the Financial Services Industry. Our cutting edge software is used by some of the worlds most well-known brands. Our secure platform is built with the latest Machine Learning technologies and helps our clients see anywhere from 30-40% performa</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Machine-Learning-Engineer-Computer-Vision-Job-Denver-CO-US-221941123.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221941123</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 05:08:58 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mid-Level Machine Learning Engineer - Facial Recognition</title>
      <description>CA-Hidden Hills, THIS IS AN URGENT / IMMEDIATE HIRE If you are a mid-level Machine Learning Engineer with experience, please read on! Based in beautiful, Calabasas, we are well-established and highly innovative software company dominating the space of human identification technology and solutions. With over 10 years of R&amp;D studies, and 100+ patents issued/pending patents, we continue to be a true market leader in </description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Mid-Level-Machine-Learning-Engineer-Facial-Recognition-Job-Hidden-Hills-CA-US-221941644.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221941644</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 05:11:18 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Engineer, Computer Vision</title>
      <description>WA-Seattle, Position: Machine Learning Engineer with Computer Vision experience Location: 100% Remote Salary: DOE We are an industry leading SaaS Company known for our AI-powered solutions! Our cutting edge software suite empowers businesses of all sizes to optimize their data on a secure platform! We now have an urgent need for a Machine Learning Engineer with a strong Computer Vision background to join our </description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Machine-Learning-Engineer-Computer-Vision-Job-Seattle-WA-US-221941044.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221941044</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 05:08:36 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Researcher- (Generative Adversarial Networks)</title>
      <description>VA-Herndon, If you are a Machine Learning Engineer with experience, please read on! Located in Reston, VA, we are a fast-paced start up looking to redefine the content management experience and change how content is delivered to our customers using machine learning and computer vision. Currently, we are looking to expand our team and are in need of a skilled Machine Learning Engineer! What You Will Be Doing C</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Machine-Learning-Researcher-Generative-Adversarial-Networks-Job-Herndon-VA-US-221941972.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221941972</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 05:12:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer</title>
      <description>CA-West Menlo Park, If you are a Senior level Machine Learning Engineer with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us - Competitive salary, bonus plus equity - Room to grow with a growing startup - Make a difference in people's health What You Will Be Doing We are a growing startup focused on health and looking to add a senior level Machine Learning engineer with very strong academic credentials in mod</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Senior-Machine-Learning-Engineer-Job-West-Menlo-Park-CA-US-221942216.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221942216</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 05:13:54 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Machine Learning Engineer - Chatbot</title>
      <description>CA-San Francisco, If you are a Senior Machine Learning Engineer with NLP experience, please read on! Location: 100% remote however you must be located in the Bay area. (This will be remote forever but we want people to be in the local area for quartly team outings) Job Summary: The Chatbot team is building a Recruiting conversational assistant - a virtual assistant to help job seekers find the right opportunity. Ou</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Senior-Machine-Learning-Engineer-Chatbot-Job-San-Francisco-CA-US-221982494.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221982494</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 05:11:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Engineer - Remote</title>
      <description>Telecommute/home-based, Rezult continues to make great strides toward enhancing the technology community nationwide. We are consistently looking for qualified professionals to join us in achieving success. Currently we are searching for a Machine Learning Engineer to fulfill an immediate vacancy. This individual will be responsible for: Design and develop algorithms for challenging vision classification and detections pr</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Machine-Learning-Engineer-Remote-Job-US-221033563.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221033563</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:09:35 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Scientist / Machine Learning Specialist</title>
      <description>TX-Houston, Genuent is hiring a Data Scientist. This would be a direct hire opportunity located in Houston, TX. If this is something you might be interested in, please send your updated resume to Mike Sabo: MSabo@genuent.com *Due to client restrictions, we are only accepting those authorized to work in the US without visa sponsorship now or in the future* As a Data Scientist / Machine Learning Specialist, you</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Data-Scientist-Machine-Learning-Specialist-Job-Houston-TX-US-221118117.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221118117</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:14:55 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robotics and Machine Learning Software Engineer III</title>
      <description>MO-Kansas City, Innovate to solve the world's most important challenges The future is what you make it. When you join Honeywell, you become a member of our global team of thinkers, innovators, dreamers, and doers who make the things that make the future. Working at Honeywell isn’t just about developing cool things. That’s why all of our employees enjoy access to dynamic career opportunities across different field</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Robotics-Machine-Learning-Software-Engineer-III-Job-Kansas-City-MO-US-221527559.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221527559</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:08:57 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning/Emulation Engineer</title>
      <description>CA-Mountain View, · Thorough understanding of complete chip development life cycle · Very good understanding of EDA and other design tools used by chip design companies · Very good understanding of how engineers use the above tools in their work · The candidate must have strong communication skills · The candidate must have strong presentation skills · The candidate must have strong experience in developing technic</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Machine-Learning-Emulation-Engineer-Job-Mountain-View-CA-US-221568465.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221568465</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:08:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Operator</title>
      <description>TN-Jackson, Do prefer to work in an air conditioned environment? Are you open to learning a new skill set? Are you seeking a position with a growing company? If you looking for all of these things, this is the job for you! This company is growing and has recenlty expanded its operation allowing for opportunities for advancement. This position, as a Robotic Welder, is automated, so it is easy to operate and ea</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Machine-Operator-Job-Jackson-TN-US-221161763.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221161763</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:06:43 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Operator/Press</title>
      <description>TN-Mount Pleasant, Do you enjoy working in a fast-paced production environment? Do you like working with your hands and learning new skills? We have a client in Mt. Pleasant, TN that is looking to add to their team. If you are detail-oriented and have prior manufacturing exerience and and good work history , then we want to hear from you! Responsibilities Must have prior manufacturing experience and stable work hist</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Machine-Operator-Press-Job-Mount-Pleasant-TN-US-221586165.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221586165</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:18:24 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Operator - Plywood</title>
      <description>NC-Brogden, Description Georgia-Pacific is looking for motivated individuals to join our team as Machine Operators . Successful candidates will have the opportunity to operate various types of equipment in order to meet production goals and to ensure a safe work environment. Machine Operators will also perform basic care duties such as preventative maintenance on machinery or repairing minor issues. If you ar</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Machine-Operator-Plywood-Job-Brogden-NC-US-221142867.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221142867</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:06:17 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instructor- CNC Machine Operators</title>
      <description>CT-Waterbury, Nesco Resource is looking for CNC Instructors in Waterbury, CT. Instructor will be teaching CNC Operator skills (Mill &amp; Lathe) in a trade school environment on a part-time basis. 8:00 AM to 12:00 PM, Monday- Friday. Hourly pay is $27.00/hour for right candidate. Responsibilities and Duties: Manage, organize, and teach CNC Operation (Mill &amp; Lathe) Create syllabi, course materials, and assignments t</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Instructor-CNC-Machine-Operators-Job-Waterbury-CT-US-221160221.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221160221</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:06:44 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Operator</title>
      <description>TN-Jackson, Do prefer to work in an air conditioned environment? Are you open to learning a new skill set? Are you seeking a position with a growing company? If you looking for all of these things, this is the job for you! This company is growing and has recenlty expanded its operation allowing for opportunities for advancement. This position, as a Robotic Welder, is automated, so it is easy to operate and ea</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Machine-Operator-Job-Jackson-TN-US-221963252.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221963252</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 14:19:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Operator</title>
      <description>NY-Brentwood, Are you looking to work with an Essential Employer within a long term role, with an opportunity for steady overtime? We are currently seeking night shift machine operators to work at one of Long Island's Top Employers! Position involves learning to use a mail machine in a temperature controlled warehouse. Basic computer skills and atttention to detail is required. Also must have the ability to sta</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Machine-Operator-Job-Brentwood-NY-US-221552893.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221552893</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:13:15 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACHINE OPERATOR-FLAVORING 3RD SHIFT</title>
      <description>MN-Albert Lea, Training to be able to tend to fluid beds during the flavoring process of food ingredient powders. Responsibilities: Basic mechanical aptitude by using machine specific tools. Ability to work safely when learning the equipment and surroundings Properly lock out and tag out equipment. Good Manufacturing Practices (GMPs) and how to keep the product safe Assist coworkers in loading product and packag</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/MACHINE-OPERATOR-FLAVORING-3RD-SHIFT-Job-Albert-Lea-MN-US-221118161.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221118161</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:14:56 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instructor- Davenport Screw Machine</title>
      <description>CT-Waterbury, Nesco Resource is looking for CNC Instructors in Waterbury, CT. Instructor will be teaching CNC Operator skills (Mill &amp; Lathe) in a trade school environment on a part-time basis. 8:00 AM to 12:00 PM, Monday- Friday. Hourly pay is $27.00/hour for right candidate. Responsibilities and Duties: Manage, organize, and teach CNC Operation (Mill &amp; Lathe) Create syllabi, course materials, and assignments t</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Instructor-Davenport-Screw-Machine-Job-Waterbury-CT-US-221562111.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221562111</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 00:17:05 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Engineer</title>
      <description>CA-Mountain View, Job Description Data Engineer Full Time opportunity in Mountain View, CA We are looking for a Data Engineer to join our team and advance our mission of improving metabolic health and reverse chronic diseases using IoT and Machine Learning. Responsibilities Designand develop backend microservices using technologies such as Spring Boot, REST APIs, Protobufs, Python, SQL databases, Time Series databa</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Data-Engineer-Job-Mountain-View-CA-US-221996340.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221996340</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 09:22:22 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientist - Disease Modeling - Mammalian Cell Culture, FACS</title>
      <description>CA-South San Francisco, If you are a Scientist with 2+ years of Disease Modeling experience, high throughput IPSC differentiation techniques, and in-vitro modeling, please read on! Located right in southern San Francisco, we are a data-driven drug discovery and development company that uses machine learning and high-throughput biology to transform drug discovery initiatives, which are delivered to our patients. We use hi</description>
      <link>http://jobview.monster.com/Scientist-Disease-Modeling-Mammalian-Cell-Culture-FACS-Job-South-San-Francisco-CA-US-221981865.aspx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="False">221981865</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 05:04:07 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>